Moira Kielbiski

C:306.401.7116

kielbiski@yahoo.com

PROFILE

I am a bilingual communications specialist with experience in emergency telecommunications and dispatch, customer service, and a freelance passion for graphic design. I feel suited for a position requiring an experienced communications specialist that can produce and create content for your organization.

SKILLS

- Second Language Evaluation (French): Reading (X) Written (B) Oral (C)
- The capacity to effectively establish and maintain effective working relationships with clients.
- Developing and maintaining corporate image and identity, including the approved use of logos and signage.
- A proven ability to create logos, develop, and maintain web pages.

TECHNICAL

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Dreamweaver
- GIMP (image manipulation, similar to Adobe Photoshop)
- Inkscape (scalable vector graphics, similar to Adobe Illustrator)
- Scribus (desktop publisher, similar to Adobe PageMaker or InDesign)
- Web page creation and editing software
- Microsoft Office Suite (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Access)
- Mac OS and Windows platforms

COMMUNICATIONS EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Telecommunications Operator, RCMP

2017-Present

Quickly and accurately process calls, and prioritize information to ensure officer and public safety in a high-stress, face-paced environment. Obtain all the required information so an appropriate level of response can be provided as effectively as possible. Dispatch officers and anticipate their needs, ensuring they have relevant and timely information to keep themselves and the public safe. Follow federal and divisional policy.

Graphics and Design, Independent Contractor

2003-2017

Use creative and technological skills to meet the needs of businesses and organizations through logo design, branding, social media, and marketing. Consult with clients to determine their goals, gather information and present solutions. Create vector graphic elements, documents and campaigns; design and produce posters, event tickets, and apparel. Establish social media presence. Responsive website development and maintenance using languages including HTML and CSS. Compile Google analytics and report the results. Clients included: Lost Creek Outfitters, Carrot River Minor Hockey Association, Blessings in a Backpack, Carrot River Outdoors Club, Carrot River Young Women's Club, Curious Kidz Preschool.

Portfolio: https://mkielbiski.github.io/

Advertising/Member-at-large, Carrot River Young Women's Club

2013-2015

Work with group members to plan and coordinate events benefiting children and families, including the advertising campaign for a major fundraiser. Revitalize and create new materials for the Christmas hamper program. Establish a social media presence for the group.

Computer Graphic Artist, Global Television, Regina

1999-2003

Use various software programs, including 2D and 3D animation, to create and compose graphics for advertising and news programming, developing and implementing templates for cohesiveness. Coordinate campaigns over various media, including print and television, while ensuring corporate compliance and brand identity. Collaborate with writers and producers to develop elements for their projects. Establish and maintain internal and external contacts.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Rose Valley Pharmacy, Customer Service

2016-2017

Respond to customer enquiries; operate point of sale system for pharmacy and liquor vendor; maintain client confidentiality.

SLGA - Carrot River Liquor Store, Customer Service

2015

Operate SLGA point of sale system; ensure the legal sale of alcohol; order and receive alcohol shipments; accurately complete paperwork to open and close the store independently; follow government policy.

Treasurer, Carrot River Elementary School Community Council

2012-2015

Maintain balanced books; create monthly and annual reports, issue cheques, make deposits, records expenses and income.

Customer Service, Gloria's Family Restaurant, Carrot River

2012-2015

Adapt to a continually changing environment as the only server in a busy restaurant; participate as a team member in the kitchen and work independently when needed.

Secretary, Curious Kids Preschool Coop Board, Carrot River

2011-2012

Record minutes and refer to the Cooperative's policy as required.

Secretary/Member-at-Large, Kinette Club of Sturgis

2003-2008

Organize events; record and distribute minutes; collect committee reports.

Coordinator, Sturgis Block Parent Association

2005-2008

Revitalize the program by obtaining funding to return the Association to good standing; update and maintain records; recruit new volunteers and coordinate volunteer screening.

EDUCATION

Saskatchewan Polytechnic, Business Administration Program

2016-2017

Completed the following courses through distance education: Introduction to Human Resource Management, Business Communications, Business Mathematics, Introduction to Financial Accounting I.

University of Regina, Department of Fine Arts

1997-1999

Accepted a full-time position at Global Television in my desired field in the third year of BFA (Film and Video Production).

Sheldon-Williams Collegiate, Regina, Grade 12 Diploma

1991-1995